# **Dane Middleton**

middletondane@gmail.com · (847) 363 1986 · Austin, TX LinkedIn · https://www.linkedin.com/in/dane-middleton/

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Full-Stack JavaScript academy graduate with fundamental web development skills and 9+ years utilizing collaboration technologies to create more cohesive team environments. With problemsolving patience and effective group communication skills I am searching for an organization that places high value on learning, discovery, information sharing, and career development.

#### CORE COMPETENCIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, jQuery, Git, Project Management, Salesforce, Cisco Collaboration Services, Microsoft Applications, Enterprise Tech Sales, SaaS, UCaaS, Cloud Computing

#### **EDUCATION**

**Austin Coding Academy** 

**MERN Stack** 

#### International TEFL Academy

120-hour certification teaching English as a second language

# Macquarie University, Sydney, Australia

Study Abroad

## Western Michigan University, Kalamazoo, Michigan

- Bachelor of Arts in Film, Video and Media Studies; Philosophy Minor
- Dean's List/Graduated with Honors
- Lambda Pi Eta Communication Honor Society

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Austin Coding Academy, Austin, TX Graduate

01/2018 to 11/2018

- Knowledgeable in MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, JavaScript, CSS and HTML as well as the principles and techniques of website construction and maintenance.
- Utilized MERN stack knowledge to build production-ready gettingpaid roommate billing application

# West Unified Communications Services, Austin, TX **Channel Manager**

12/2015 to 06/2017

- Responsible for largest master agent relationship and 30+ master agents \$7 million+ book of business
- Increased annual revenue with top software account 35% through leading a global team of sales and support contacts, adapting to language barriers and focusing on connecting 5K+ employees and their customers with our technologies
- Tripled video networking usage of key aerospace and defense account through training power users to integrate services and by focusing on value of cloud security

# **West Unified Communications Services,** Austin, TX **Channel Account Manager**

03/2012 to 12/2015

- Exceeded yearly revenue targets 2013 & 2014
- First remote worker to receive Channel Manager promotion due to high levels of accountability, collaboration, growth, and problem-solving abilities
- Implemented 500+ new monthly users for collaboration services with online portal access by redesigning Excel reports for processing
- Improved partner experience by creating training videos to tackle common requests

# West Unified Communications Services Chicago, IL Account Executive

05/2011 to 03/2012

- First employee to close \$60K Virtual Environment contract with fortune 500 account by quickly learning new technology and engaging with product manager
- Increased \$1 million+ base of global business by redesigning Salesforce reports and utilizing integrated event logging technologies
- Incorporated monthly discovery meetings for enterprise accounts to educate decision makers on new products and features, troubleshoot tech issues, identify opportunities, and provide recommendations

# West Unified Communications Services Chicago, IL Collaborations Specialist

03/2008 to 05/2011

- Recognized as the Collaborations Specialist of the Year in 2010
- Increased team revenue by mentoring new colleagues through daily Q&A sessions
- Utilized communication skills to improve 80+ daily cold call success rate by identifying team needs through research, networking & extensive product knowledge
- Managed daily web training demonstrations on Cisco, Adobe, & Microsoft tools

#### **ACTIVITIES**

Adventure Traveler • Marathoner • Triathlete • Avid Reader • Francophone Film Festival Organizer • RAGBRAI Bike Tour Participant • Salsa, Kombucha and Candle Maker • KUTX Radio Volunteer • Austin Pets Alive! Volunteer • Centro Romero TEFL Tutor